JOON PARK

(213) 618-9347 | <u>isp220@gmail.com</u> | San Diego, CA

github.com/jsp220 | LinkedIn

SUMMARY

A former Bioprocess Engineer with 8+ years of biotech industry experience looking to pivot into a software/web developer/engineer role. Open to Junior- and Associate-level front end, back end, or full stack positions where I will be able to utilize skills and knowledge gained from UCSD's full stack bootcamp as well as continue to learn and grow as a software engineer.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS, CSS libraries Bootstrap, Materialize
- MERN Stack MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js
- React-router
- REST APIs
- Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)
- ¡Query
- SQL databases MySQL
- NoSQL databases MongoDB
- ODM/ORMs Sequelize, Mongoose, Apollo GraphQL, apollo-client

- Model-View-Controller (MVC)
- Handlebars
- Test frameworks Jest
- Progressive Web Apps using Webpacks, Service Workers, IndexedDB
- Version control using Git
- SDLC practices (Agile)
- shell commands
- Wireframing
- Python
- Socket.io

RECENT PROJECTS

Cats vs. Dogs - https://young-bayou-37103.herokuapp.com/

November 2022

- An interactive real-time word game app similar to a board/party game called Codenames
- Technologies used: MERN stack, Socket.io, JWT, animate.css, react-router, styled-components, graphQL, apollo-client, apollo-server-express, mongoose

Corgis Messenger - https://radiant-peak-12110.herokuapp.com/

October 2022

- A Chat app that allows real-time messaging and notifies users when messages are received
- Technologies used: Express is, MySQL/Sequelize, Socket io, Handlebars, Bootstrap, doteny, deployment via Heroku

Fullstech Blog - https://fullstech-blog.herokuapp.com/

October 2022

- A web blog that allows users to create an account, post and edit text blog posts, and add comments
- Technologies used: Express.js, MySQL/Sequelize, Handlebars, Bootstrap, MVC design pattern

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Process Engineer II, Manufacturing, Halozyme Therapeutics, San Diego, CA

May 2021 - July 2022

Senior Engineer, CMC Gene Therapy Development, Neurocrine Biosciences, San Diego, CA January 2020 – March 2021

Process Development Engineer III, Tocagen Inc., San Diego, CA

February 2019 - December 2019

Process Development Engineer II

April 2016 – February 2019

Process Development Engineer I

May 2014 - April 2016

SAT/ACT Math Instructor, Elite Educational Institute, San Diego, CA

April 2015 – September 2015

Clinical Monitoring Associate, PAREXEL International, San Diego, CA

January 2014 - May 2014

EDUCATION

Certification of Completion, Full Stack Web Development

University of California, San Diego Extended Studies

November 2022 La Jolla, CA

Master of Science in Bioengineering

University of California, San Diego

June 2013 La Jolla, CA

Bachelor of Science in Bioengineering: Biotechnology

University of California, San Diego

June 2011

La Jolla, CA

• Jacobs School Scholar – a full scholarship for all four years, given by the School of Engineering to select top incoming freshmen in engineering majors each year